(至今走过的路)
萨姆
Sam!
你得发誓不会想方设法救我回来
You got to promise not to try to bring me back.
小萨姆
Sammy?
你是猎魔人  现在你弟弟又出现了
You're a hunter. Now you know your brother's out there.
我要你去
I need you to go.
萨姆  他有点不对劲
It's Sam. He's different.
他的灵魂  不见了
It's his soul. It's gone.
我现在去地狱带回你弟弟的灵魂
I'm going to go to hell to fetch your brother's soul.
我啥都不记得了
I don't remember anything.
找到炼狱对我而言才是重中之重
Finding purgatory's important to me --
一个满是灵魂却未被开发过的油井
An untapped oil well of every fanged,clawed soul.
你们清楚灵魂有多珍贵吗
Do you have any idea what souls are worth?
它们有什么力量吗
What power they hold?
拉斐尔和他的追随者
Raphael and his followers,
他们想让他去统治天堂
They want him to rule heaven.
我们最不想看到的  就是他掌权
The last thing we want is to let him take over.
那小英国佬数月前被烧得灰飞烟灭了
That little limey mook roasted months ago.
克劳力还活着
Crowley's alive.
-我想来谈笔简单的交易  -跟我
- I want to discuss a simple business transaction. - With me?
你勾结了克劳力合伙找炼狱
U and crowley have been going after purgatory together?
我能阻止拉斐尔
I can stop Raphael.
你得相信我
You have to trust me.
(如今)
(交货入口)
已经关门了
We're closed.
就  就一会儿
Just,uh -- just give me a second.
抱歉  伙计  我们中午才营业
Sorry,pal. We -- we open at noon.
听着  你不明白
Look, you don't understand.
好吧  我想我非常明白是怎么回事
Okay, I-I think I understand...just fine.
我不想惹麻烦  说真的  你赶紧走吧
Look, I-I don't need this kind of hassle, so, seriously, just get the hell out.
求你了  给我一分钟让我想想办法就行
Please. Please, just give me a minute to think, that's all.
之后绝不打扰你  就一分钟  拜托了
Then I'm out of your hair. One minute, please.
你叫什么
What's your name?
我不知道
I don't know.
不知道是什么意思
What do you mean you don't know?
我不记得了  什么都不记得了
I mean I don't remember. I don't remember anything.
[邪恶力量 第6季第22集]
得了  你少跟我扯蛋了
Come on. You're dickin' with me.
全都忘了吗
Nothing?
都说了  一片空白
I'm telling you -- blank slate.
你总有钱包  身份证吧
Well, you got a wallet, I.D.?
我也希望我有
I wish I did.
好吧  那你最后记得的事是什么
Okay, what's the last thing you remember?
我在公园的长椅上醒来
I woke up on a park bench,
警察的手电在我脸上晃  他们想抓我
cops shoving a flashlight in my face, trying to take me in.
所以你跑了
So you ran.
不  我  我把他们撂倒了  俩个都撂倒了
No, I, um I knocked them out cold, both of them.
不  我也不想的
No, look. I didn't mean to.
只是发生的太快了  懂吗
It just happened really fast, you know?
我  我觉得那是本能什么的
I-I think I-instinct or something, I guess.
-这本能挺给力啊  -对  可不是么
- That's some instinct. - Yeah, tell me about it.
正常人谁会有这种身手啊
I mean, who even knows how to do something like that?
先带你去急诊室  那些个医生们会治好你
We'll get you to the E.R. the --the quacks will hash it out.
不
No.
你必须去
Try "Yeah."
你这样相当不正常
Look, the bats have flown the belfry.
-你需要看医生  -不  我
- You need to see a doctor. - No,I...
我没时间
I don't have time.
你急着要干嘛
Time for what?
这很难道明
Look, it's hard to explain.
我总觉得  我必须得赶去什么地方
I just feel like I-I have to...be somewhere.
必须得阻止什么事发生
There's s-something I got to stop.
婚礼吗  还是赶火车
Oh, like a wedding? A train?
不  很重要的事  是事关生死  事关...
No, something important, something like...life or death,like-
明白  好啦  放轻松
OK!-- hey,hey,hey. Just relax.
你逼是逼不出来的  所以  不如顺其自然
Y-you can't poop it out. So, just -- it'll come to you.
怎么了
What is it?
(H. P.洛夫克拉夫特  《猎黑行者》)
你是恐怖小说迷吗
You a horror fan?
是啊  大概吧
Yeah,um,I think so.
真的  真有可能
You know,I really think so.
这东西有点...
Something -- something about this.
菲利浦不是他的姓  是洛夫克萊夫特
Phillips ain't his last name. It's Lovecraft.
真的  你该去医院了
Seriously,we are taking you to a doctor.
你有电脑吗
Have you got a computer?
什么
What?
就是它  存在的  两个镇之外
That's it. It exists. Look -- two towns over.
-你认为自己住在这破地方么  -也许
- You think you're staying in this dump? - Maybe.
也许你是个鸭
Maybe you're a hooker.
回头就知道了
I guess I'll find out.
你看  我不知道该说什么
Look,um... I don't know what to say.
谢谢你做的这一切
Thanks for everything.Y,uh-
你想去哪里
Where do you think you're going?
我没事的
I'll be fine.
你刚刚还突然犯病了呢
Says the head case that just slumped over a minute ago.
我要怎么说你才会去医院
Look,is there any way I can convince you to go to a hospital?
不去了  显然我是个固执的人
No. Apparently,I'm stubborn.
我也是啊
So am I.
我来开车
I'm driving.
感谢你的好意  但是不必了
Look,that's really nice of you but not necessary.
-真的吗  你脑子很不清醒  -但是
- Really? Okay,look,your eggs are scrambled. - But --
没什么但是
But nothing.
不是  我是说  我是个陌生人
No,I mean,I'm -- I'm just some guy.
我可能是个坏人  你一定是疯了
I-I could be anybody. You got to be nuts.
这话别人对我说过
I've been called that.
如果让你自己走了
Look,if I let you go off alone,
我会夜不能寐的
I won't be able to sleep at night.
说实话  我很想知道真相如何
And,honestly,I'm dying to know how it all turns out.
那么  从哪开始
So,uh,where do we start?
一层  拐角房间
Uh,ground floor,corner room...
最接近逃生口
Nearest to the fire escape.
是我的话就选那间房  逃跑最方便
That's the one I'd pick -- quickest getaway.
你怎么知道这些
And why do you know that?
我就是知道
I just do.
有信用卡吗
Hey,you got a credit card?
干嘛  我们要入住吗
Why? Are we,uh,checking in?
差不多
Sort of.
老兄
Dude...
你到底是谁
Who are you?
问得好
Good question.
这都是你的吗
This all yours?
不知道
I don't know.
可能吧
I guess.
我喜欢你这里的装饰
Well,I love what you've done with the place.
有点《美丽心灵》加《七宗罪》的味道
It's very "Beautiful mind" Meets..."se7en."
不好意思  我一紧张就乱说
Sorry. I talk when I'm nervous.
看来我们知道你叫什么了
Hey,well,I guess we know your name.
很高兴见到你  吉米·佩奇
Nice to meet you,Jimmy page.
或者  尼尔·佩尔特
And,uh,Neil peart.
或者  安格斯·杨
And Angus young.
听着  请别介意
Okay,listen,no offense,
但是  我有点被吓坏了
But I'm...really starting to freak out.
我也是
You and me both.
她在哪
Where is she?
她说在这里等她
She said to meet her here.
我再打给她试试
I'll try her again.
埃莉
Elle?
-看来我还是需要你帮忙  -别乱动
- I guess I could have used your help after all. - Just be still.
-怎么回事  -他们抓走了我
- What happened? - They took me.
我跑掉了
I got away.
埃莉
Oh,Ellie.
他们对你做了什么
Oh,what have they done to you?
什么都做了
Everything.
恶魔我还能对付
The demon I could have handled,you know?
但是当天使一出面...
But when the angel stepped in...
我告诉他了  鲍比
I told him,Bobby.
他们已经做好打开炼狱的准备了
They have enough to crack purgatory wide open.
告诉我吧  我得知道
Tell me. I need to know.
他们需要处女的鲜血
They need virgin blood.
那对他们来说是小菜一碟
That's a milk run for them.
他们还需要炼狱生物的鲜血
And they need the blood of a purgatory native.
他们也已经搞到很多了
Well, they've got plenty of that now.
他们已经把门打开了吗
Have they opened it yet?
明天行动
Tomorrow.
要等到月蚀才行
The moon and the eclipse.
抱歉  鲍比
I'm sorry, Bobby.
-不  没关系的  -我真的很抱歉
- No, it's okay. - I'm sorry, really.
告诉我们他们在哪里
Just tell us where they are.
埃莉
Elle?
我对此事深表遗憾
I'm sorry this had to happen.
克劳力丧心病狂了
Crowley got carried away.
难道跟你一点关系都没有么  你个王八蛋
Yeah, I bet it was all Crowley, you son of a bitch!
你还没醒悟  对吧
You don't even see it, do you?
不知道自己已经完全失控了
How totally off the rails you are.
够了
Enough!
我不在乎你对我的看法
I don't care what you think.
我已经向你解释过了  但你却听不进去
I've tried to make you understand. You won't listen.
所以我不妨直说了
So let me make this simple.
拜托你回家吧  让我来阻止拉斐尔
Please go home and let me stop Raphael.
这话我不会说第二遍
I won't ask again.
很好  因为我想你已经猜到答案了
Well, good, 'cause I think you already know the answer.
真希望事情没有发展到这一步
I wish it hadn't come to this.
有一点你可以放心  等这一切结束以后
Well, rest assured, when this is all over...
我会救萨姆的
I will save Sam,
但前提是你不能插手
But only if you stand down.
为什么要救萨姆
Save Sam from what?
喂  喂  你还好吗
Hey, hey. Are you okay?
萨姆
Sam.
我叫萨姆
My name is sam.
那么  你都记起了什么
So, uh, what do you remember?
那个
Well,
这种话说出来会显得很奇怪
it might sound pretty strange if I said it aloud.
不可能比现在更奇怪了
Oh,it -- it couldn't get any stranger.
是吗  别过早下结论
Yeah? Don't be so sure.
我说不清
Look, I-I don't know.
因为只是些零碎的记忆
I mean, it's all pretty spotty, you know?
我只记得我当时...我和...
I just remember I was -- I was with, uh --
两个男人在一起
with two guys.
其中一个有男模的范儿
One was, like, a male-model type,
而另一个是个老头  叫做...
And the other was an older guy named, uh...
鲍比
Bobby.
好吧  你在找什么
Okay. Well, what are you looking for?
找到了  鲍比·辛格  就是他了
Here. Bobby singer. That has to be it.
上面有他的电话吗
Is there a phone number?
没有  只有个地址  南达科他州苏瀑
No, just an address. Sioux Falls, South Dakota.
南达科他州
South Dakota.
好的...
Okay, uh...
听着  萨姆
L-listen, Sam --
-你是叫萨姆吧  -对
- Sam, right? - Yeah.
我真的很抱歉  但我要...
Look, I'm really sorry, but this is --
就此跟你道别了
is where I got to get off.
不必道歉  没问题
Oh, no. Of course. No problem.
好的  那你打算怎么过去
Okay. Well, how are you gonna get there?
看来我可以开车过去
I guess I'll take my car.
那辆就是我的
That's mine.
-你确定吗  -相当确定
- Are you sure? - Oh, yeah.
听着  萨姆
Look, Sam,
我觉得你就这样离开不太好
I don't feel right about you going off like this.
别担心
Oh, look, don't worry.
你为我做得已经够多了
Y-you've done way too much for me already.
我不是那个意思
That's not what I mean.
我的意思是...
What I mean is, uh...
我有种不详的预感
I've got a bad feeling, you know,
看到你的那些假身份证和那个阴暗的房间
With those I.D.s and that shady-ass hotel room.
不管你到底在寻找什么
Whatever you're looking for --
最终的结果可能十分不妙
You might not like what you find.
我难道还有别的选择吗
What other choice do I have?
你可以在这里多待一段时间
You could stick around here a little bit longer,
等头脑清醒了再决定
Get your head straight,
而不是草率地离开  盲目地...
instead of going off, flying blind into --
怎么回事
What the hell was that?!
趴着别动
Stay down.
萨姆
Sam!
小萨姆
Sammy.
Sammy?
拜托  醒过来啊
Come on. Snap out of it.
如何了
Anything?
我不能这样坐视不理  鲍比  我得帮他
I can't just sit here, Bobby. I've got to help him.
-迪恩  -让他逃离梦境什么的
- Dean. - You know, "Dreamscape" his noggin, something.
你知道小卡做了什么
You know what Cass did.
你弟弟脑子里那道屏障没了
The dam inside your brother's head is gone,
所有地狱的记忆都倾巢而出
and all hell's spilling loose.
-我们不知道里面什么情况  -我不管
- We don't know what's going on inside. - I don't care.
-我们必须得做点什么  -我们会做的
- We have got to do something! - And we will.
但现在离他们打开炼狱之门只剩十六小时
But right now we got 16 hours till they pop purgatory.
这已经少了一个人了
I'm down one man.
我不能再失去另一个了
I can't afford to be down two.
是啊  那事我们有什么进展呢
Yeah, and how's that going,huh?
我们不知道克劳力在哪
We've got no line on Crowley.
也不知道小卡在哪  巴尔萨泽也玩失踪
We got no line on Cass. Balthazar's M.I.A.
我们只知道
I mean, all we've got
萨姆莫名其妙就昏迷不醒
is Sam going through whatever the hell this is!
你知道
You know...
小卡要的就是这种效果
...this is exactly what Cass wants...
要你崩溃
for you to fall to pieces.
想想萨姆会想要我们做什么
Just try to think of what Sam would want.
找到小卡  鲍比
Find Cass, Bobby.
马上找到他
Find him now.
你闻到威士忌的味道了吗
Do you smell whiskey?
拜托  萨姆  能不能专心点
Okay, Sam, would you focus?
好  抱歉
Yeah. I'm sorry.
好吧  刚才是谁冲我们开枪
Okay, so, who shot at us?
我没看清楚
I-I didn't really get a good look.
我们得去报警
We got to go to the cops.
不行  只要我们能找到我朋友
No. Look, if we can just get to my friends,
我知道他们能帮我们
they can help us, I know it.
你不知道他们是不是你的朋友
Okay, you don't know if they're your friends, okay?
你什么都不知道
You don't know anything about anything.
-调头吧  -不行
- Just turn around. - No.
-你跟我在一起更安全  -你怎么知道
- Look, you're safer with me. - How do you know that?
你吓着我了
You're scaring me.
神马  不可能啊
What? No way.
你刚才干嘛啊
What was that?
你啥意思  现在是白天了
What do you mean? It's daylight.
那又怎样
Yeah?
刚刚还是晚上呢  现在是白天了
It was night, and now it's day.
一直都是白天
It was always day.
不不不不不  不是的
No, no, no, no, no. No,it wasn't. It...
这是怎么回事啊
what the hell is going on here?
好吧  今天真是疯够了
Okay, so I am all filled up on crazy for today.
这样吧  萨姆  再见了您
You know what, Sam? I'll-I'll see you.
等等  等等  嘿  嘿  嘿
Wait, wait, wait. Hey, hey, hey.
上车
Get in the car.
我的天
My God.
我就这么挫的吗
Am I really that gawky?
好啊  小哥
Howdy.
这不可能
This is impossible.
错  再想想
Cold. Try again.
这  这是幻觉
I'm, uh, I'm hallucinating.
接近
Warmer.
不过你看  一般来说
But see, normally,
产生幻觉的时候  你至少还是醒着的
you're awake when you're tripping balls.
我在做梦啊
I'm dreaming?
刚刚有人赢了主场比赛哟
And someone just won a copy of the home game.
我们在你的脑子里呢  萨姆
We're inside your grapefruit, Sam.
孩子  你被施咒了
Son... you've been juiced.
我什么都不记得了
I-I-I don't remember anything.
你的闺蜜小卡把地狱屏障弄倒了
Well, your B.F.F. Cass brought the hell wall tumbling down,
而你呢  你个可悲的小屁孩
and you, pathetic infant that you are,
就零落成碎片了
shattered into pieces.
我们都是其中一片
Piece...piece.
我不知道你在说什么
I-I have no idea what you're talking about.
你怎么会明白呢
Why would you?
你这么废柴  哪像我
You're jello, pal, unlike me.
你是什么
What are you?
我是无缺陷的
I'm not handicapped.
没有那劳什子的灵魂
I'm not saddled with a soul.
事实上呢  这副肉身我使唤了一阵呢
In fact, I used to skipper this meatboat for a while.
一切都得心应手  我敏锐而且坚强
It was smooth sailing. I was sharp, strong.
后来他们就把灵魂给你装回去了
That is, till they crammed your soul back in.
你看看你现在
Now look at you.
还是以前那副双眼迷蒙没骨气的狗狗样
Same misty-eyed milksop you always were.
因为灵魂本就脆弱
That's because souls are weak.
纯粹是种负担
They're a liability.
现在呢  不是我恨你  不过话得说清楚
Now, nothing personal, but run the numbers.
在事情不可挽救之前  总得有人掌控局面
Someone's got to take charge around here before it's too late.
出来  出来呀  你躲到哪儿去了
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
你以为我很坏
You think I'm bad?
等你见了另一个就知道了
Wait till you meet the other one.
小萨姆  萨姆
Sammy! Sam!
我想起了我是谁
I remember who I am...
一年来我做过的每一件事
Everything I did this past year.
想起了你
And I remember you.
走开  不然我杀了她
Walk away,  or the girl dies.
这回你没筹码了
There goes your leverage
我不是说过  让你回头
Didn't I tell you to turn back,
你不会喜欢你找到的答案
that you wouldn't like what you found?
对不起
I'm sorry.
非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你还会加倍遗憾的
Not as sorry as you're gonna be.
看看是谁来了
Look what the cat dragged in.
至少你这老帽把天使防护咒弄对了
Well,  at least you mudfish finally got the angel-proofing right.
睡美人怎么样了
How's sleeping beauty?
你没偷吻人家吧
You didn't steal any kisses,  I trust?
这么久你到底搞什么去了
What the hell took you so long?
要听实话
Honestly?
我在犹豫
I was having second thoughts.
-犹豫什么  -犹豫要不要帮你们
- About? - About whether to help you.
我在想我或许...
I was thinking maybe...
我或许应该反过来把你们收拾掉
maybe I should rip out your sticky bits instead.
那么你的决定是什么呢
And what did you decide?
小卡和克劳力在这个地方
Cass and Crowley are there.
好戏就在那里开场
That's where the show gets started.
等一下  拿上东西你带我们过去
All right,  well,  give us a minute to pack up and then zap us there.
不不不不  我可不这么想
Oh,  no,  no,  no,  no. I don't think so.
-巴尔萨泽  -我这是在背叛朋友
- Balthazar. - I'm betraying a friend here...
一位非常强大的朋友
A very powerful friend.
我们都一样
We all are.
所以我想  我冒的风险已经够大了
So I think I've stuck my neck out far enough already.
祝好运
Good luck.
先生  您的炼狱能量奶昔
Your Purgatory power shake,  monsieur...
一半恶鬼  一半处女
Half monster,  half virgin.
谢谢
Thank you.
你今天看起来比平时还纠结
You seem even more constipated than usual.
需要来点儿润肠的吗
Maybe get you some colon blow?
我要与你重议合作条件
I'm renegotiating our terms.
这样啊  你有何提议
Is that so? What terms do you propose?
你什么都得不到
You get nothing.
一个灵魂也不行
Not one single soul.
我忍不住注意到
Can't help notice...
好像有点儿不平等
seems a bit... unfairly weighted.
卡西迪奥  你怎么敢这样
Castiel... you wouldn't dare.
是我向你提议这个交易
I brought you this deal.
你认为我会将那样强大的力量
You think I'm handing all that power...
拱手让给地狱之王
to the king of hell?
我既不愚蠢也不邪恶
I'm neither stupid nor wicked.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
你难道忘了你才是下面那个么
Have you forgotten that you're the bottom in this relationship?
你有这些选择
Here are your options.
要么滚蛋  要么死
You either flee, or you die.
我们有约定的
We made a pact.
我都不会像这样毁约
Even I don't break contracts like this.
滚蛋
Flee...
还是死
Or die.
天啊  这世道还能相信谁啊
Boy, you can't trust anyone these days.
嘿
Hey.
Hey!
嗨  萨姆
Hi, Sam.
那么
So?
你是哪个
Which one are you?
你难道不知道吗
Don't you know?
我是记得地狱的那个
I'm the one that remembers hell.
时间到了  迪恩
Time's up, Dean.
再等一会
Just a second.
这是我们要去的地方  萨姆
All right, this is where we're gonna be, Sam.
你别再偷懒了  赶紧起来和我们汇合
So you get your lazy ass out of bed and come meet us.
小萨姆  求你了
Sammy, please.
我希望你没有来  萨姆
I wish you hadn't come, Sam.
我不得不  来都来了
I had to. I'm here, right?
在真实世界里  我在鲍比家  对吗
Out there in the real world, I'm at Bobby's, aren't I?
你怎么知道
How do you know?
我一直只能闻到老香料和威士忌的味道
This whole time, I smell nothing but old spice and whiskey.
我想如果我能回到这
I figured if I could get back here,
回到我的身体  我就能...
back to my body, I could...
我不知道
I don't know --
也许莫名就能醒过来了
I could snap out of it somehow.
不过你得先过我这一关
First, you have to go through me.
为什么
Why?
你想要醒来  就先要拼凑起
Humpty-dumpty has to put himself back together again
一个完整的自己
before he can wake up.
而我是最后一部分
And I'm the last piece.
意思是...
Which means...
我要知道你所知道的...
...I have to know what you know...
-在牢笼里所发生的事  -相信我
- ...what happened in the cage. - Trust me.
你不会想知道的
You don't want to know it.
你是对的
You're right.
但是我还是得知道
But I still have to.
萨姆  那是你无法想象的
Sam... you can't imagine.
别再继续了  回去吧
Stay here, go back,
去找那个酒保  去找杰西
find that bartender, go find Jess,
但是别这么做
but don't do this.
我了解你
I know you.
你不够坚强
You're not strong enough.
我们还是试试吧
We'll just have to see.
为什么这对你来说那么重要
Why is this so important to you?
你了解我
You know me.
你知道原因
You know why.
我不会把我哥哥一个人丢在真实世界
I'm not leaving my brother alone out there.
我不会和你动手
I'm not gonna fight you.
但这是你最后的机会
But this is your last chance.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你需要好运
You're gonna need it.
你召唤我吗  小卡
You rang, Cass?
对  我们有麻烦了
Yeah. We have a problem.
迪恩·温彻斯特正在来这的路上
Dean Winchester is on his way here.
真的吗  他怎么知道我们在这的
Really? Oh. How'd he even know where we were?
显然...我们中间有个叛徒
Apparently... we have a Judas in our midst.
太糟糕了
Holy hell.
是谁呢
Who is it?
我猜是那个可恶的小天使  对吗
I bet it's that bloody little Cherub, isn't it?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是我想让你去查出来
But I-I need you to find out.
当然  马上去  马上去
Of course. Um, right away, right away.
但是我怎么处理迪恩呢
Uh, but what do you want me to do about Dean?
什么都不做
Nothing.
我自己处理他
I'll handle him myself.
卡西迪奥
Castiel?
你没事吧
Are you all right?
先是萨姆和迪恩  现在是这个
First Sam and Dean, and now this.
在不可能的情况下我已经尽力了
I'm doing my best in impossible circumstances.
我的朋友们
My friends -- they...
抛弃了我
abandon me...
密谋反对我
plot against me.
让人十分费解
It's difficult to understand.
我不是一直在你身边吗
Well, you -- you always got little old me.
是的  你总是陪着我
Yes. I'll always have you.
小卡
Cass...
我看到有十几个  可能还不止
I count a dozen mooks, probably more.
恶魔吗
Demons?
天使
Angels.
我们要怎么对付那么多天使
Well, how the hell are we gonna take out that many angels?
不用  我们悄悄潜入
We don't. We'll ninja our way in.
赞个  直到他们听到你膝盖嘎吱响
Awesome, yeah -- till they hear your knee squeak.
闭嘴
Shut up.
怎么  你现在脸皮薄了啊
Oh, what, now you got thin skin?
没有  闭嘴
No, shut up.
你听到了吗
You hear that?
什么声音
What the hell is that?
霸王龙吗
T. Rex, maybe?
我的天啊
Holy mother of...
上车  上车
Get to the car. Get to the car.
千万不要低估了地狱之王  亲爱的
Never underestimate the king of hell, darling.
我懂很多顶级的小把戏哟
I know a lot of swell tricks.
现在  我们可以重新谈判了吧
Now, I think it's time to re-renegotiate our terms.
老兄  手心都是汗哎
Sweaty hands, mate.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你可以随便抚摸我
You can palm me all you want.
我在我新搭档的庇佑下很安全
I'm safe and sound under the wing of my new partner.
你好  卡西迪奥
Hello, Castiel.
拉斐尔
Raphael.
和恶魔合作  你自降身份吗
Consorting with demons. I thought that was beneath you.
听说你也有合作
Heard you were doing it.
听起来颇有趣
Sounded like fun.
卡西迪奥
You know, Castiel,
你说的拉斐尔各种
y-you said all sorts of shameful,
可耻可怕下流的事情
appalling, scatological things about Raphael.
我发现他  哦不  是她
I found him -- her --
其实真的很通情达理
to be really... quite reasonable.
你个蠢蛋
You fool.
拉斐尔会在眨眼之间出尔反尔然后毁灭你
Raphael will deceive and destroy you at the speed of thought.
对  对  因为你是正派大好人
Right, right, 'cause you're such a straight shooter.
她  他
She -- he --
会保护我免受伤害
has offered me protection against all comers.
用什么做交换
In exchange for what?
炼狱之血
The purgatory blood.
卡西迪奥  你真认为我会让你打开那道门
Castiel, you really think I would let you open that door?
让你吸收那么多能量
take in that much power?
只有我  才能成为新的上帝
If anyone is going to be the new god, it's me.
他会开启天启  甚至更糟的事情
He's gonna bring the apocalypse and worse.
这正是你的杰作  老兄
Hey, this is your doing, mate.
我只不过选择了对自己最有利的一方
I'm merely grabbing the best offer on the table.
现在你有两条路可走
Now, you have two options.
要么滚蛋  要么死
Flee or die.
[咒语]
鲍比
Bobby.
Bobby?
来  我们必须出去
Come on. We got to go.
[咒语]
忙着呢  先生们
Bit busy, gentlemen.
你们稍等片刻
Be with you in a moment.
[咒语]
也许我的咒语读错了
Maybe I said it wrong.
你读得完全正确
You said it perfectly.
不过你还需要这个
But what you needed was this.
明白了
I see.
这么说我们一直用的是
And we've been working with...
自然是狗血了
Dog blood. Naturally.
卡西迪奥玩够了吧你
Enough of these games, castiel.
把血给我拿来
Give us the blood.
你
You --
游戏结束了
game's over.
没看见他的瓶子都空了吗
His jar's empty.
卡西迪奥  你的仪式进展如何呢
So, Castiel, how'd your ritual go?
我看肯定比我们的强吧
Better than ours, I'll bet.
这是你无法想象的境界
You can't imagine what it's like.
成千上万的灵魂
They're all inside me --
现在统统在我身体里
millions upon millions of souls.
的确有范儿
Sounds sexy.
我退出  你们继续
Exit stage Crowley.
拉斐尔  你怎么了
Now, what's the matter, Raphael?
翅膀被人剪断了吗
Somebody clip your wings?
卡西迪奥  别这样
Castiel, please.
你肯放那个恶魔走  却不放过你自己的兄弟
You let the demon go... but not your own brother?
那恶魔对我还有用处
The demon I have plans for.
而你呢
You, on the other hand...
你们也看到了
So, you see...
是我救了你俩
I saved you.
小卡的确  谢谢你
You sure did, Cass. Thank you.
你们怀疑过我
You doubted me...
阻碍我
fought against me.
但一直以来我才是对的
But I was right all along.
小卡  你是对的  我们道歉
Okay, Cass, you were. We're sorry.
现在先降低你的危险性好吗
Let's just defuse you, okay?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你体内的能量非常巨大  很危险
You're full of nuke. It's not safe.
所以在月蚀结束前
So before the eclipse ends,
把这些灵魂送回炼狱去
let's get them souls back to where they belong.
那不可能  它们现在是我的
Oh, no. They belong with me.
小卡  它们会侵占你的大脑
No, Cass, I-it's scrambling your brain.
不  这事还没完呢
No, I'm not finished yet.
拉斐尔还有许多追随者
Raphael had many followers,
我必须
and I must...
让他们吃点苦头
punish them all severely.
听我说
Listen to me.
听着
Listen...
我知道我们之间曾经有过许多误会
I know there's a lot of bad water under the bridge.
但是我们曾经是一家人
But we were family once.
我宁愿为你而死
I'd have died for you.
有那么几次确实差点为你送命
I almost did a few times.
所以如果我们之间亲情尤在
So if that means anything to you...
求你了
Please.
我失去了莉莎  本
I've lost Lisa, I've lost Ben,
现在又失去了萨姆
And now I've lost Sam.
我真的不想连你也失去
Don't make me lose you, too.
小卡  你现在已经不需要这份力量了
You don't need this kind of juice anymore, Cass.
快舍弃那些力量  否则我们都得死
Get rid of it before it kills us all.
你这么说不过是因为我胜利了
You're just saying that because I won...
因为你害怕了
Because you're afraid.
迪恩  我们不是一家人
You're not my family, Dean.
我没有家人
I have no family.
萨姆  很高兴你醒过来了
I'm glad you made it, Sam.
但是天使之刃对我没用
But the angel blade won't work,
因为我现在已经不再是天使了
because I'm not an angel anymore.
我是新的上帝
I'm your new god.
更优秀更强大
A better one.
所以你们要卑躬屈膝
So you will bow down
向你们的主  也就是我  颂扬你们的爱戴
and profess your love unto me, your lord...
否则我就杀了你们
...or I shall destroy you.